# Ayush Jain

#### **Informatics Student**

ayushp0412@gmail.com

Irvine, CA linkedin.com/in/avush-iain-007/ github.com/AyushBot412

Current communicative computer science student with 7+ years of experience building Android applications and OOP languages, particularly in Python and Java. Eager to secure an internship or full-time position using my experience and interest with neural networks, cybersecurity, health informatics and back-end development to help aid any company I may join.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Technical Assistant | Irvine, CA

UCI – Division of Continuing Education, Oct 2021 – June 2022

- Provided ongoing video programming support to identify, fix, and test local bugs, and surveyed user feedback to implement changes that increased user satisfaction by 19%
- Aided Professors and Students with local IT security issues that arose, reducing number of user complaints by 28%
- Collaborated in a team of 20 workers to support over 30 classes per semester
- Managed a 3 building AV system to prepare for events and classes
- Updated server-side HTML code consistently, aiding clients to access information in a more secure manner and saved 15+ hours for colleagues

#### **RESEARCH PROJECTS**

# Student Researcher | Irvine, CA

UCI - Biomedical Sciences, Jan 2023 - Present

- Leading a 7-person team to implement a responsive Android Application that utilizes a TensorFlow Deep Learning model to analyze live images captured on mobile devices
- Building a EveDrop identifier by labeling 15,000 images to create a dataset in order to train YOLO object detection with Label Studio
- Deployed an AWS S3 server integration to store JSON packets of critical medical data in order to communicate with mobile devices

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Geolocation-Based Tracking**

Implemented a Life360-like Android application with authentication that made 30+ calls/hour to the GoogleMapsAPI and back-end storage in Google Firebase for security

#### **SKILLS**

Programming Languages: Python, Java, Kotlin, HTML/CSS, SQL (sqlite3) Frameworks and tools: Git/GitHub, Android Studio, VS Code, Intellil Firebase, Roboflow, Burp Suite

OS: Android, Windows

#### **EDUCATION**

### University of California - Irvine | Irvine, CA

B.S in Informatics, Sept 2021 - Present

- Relevant Coursework:
  - Advanced Python Programming with Software Libraries
  - o Programming in Java
  - Current Practice and Methodology of Software Engineering
  - o Boolean Logic and Finite Automata

## **CERTIFICATIONS/LANGUAGES**

• Lyft Virtual Experience Program Participant | English - Kannada - Hindi